Charles Bukowski papers, 1958-1988
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series V: Foreign Language Publications, 1973-1979
  - Gedichte Die Einer Schrieb Bevor Er Im 8. Stockwerk Aus Dem Fenster Sprang (selections from: Poems Written Before Jumping Out of an 8 Story Window, The Days Run Away Like Wild Horses Over the Hills, At Terror Street and Agony Way), translated by Carl Weissner, Gersthofen, Maro Verlag. 1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Nervöse Blätter1: Gedichte-Bilder-Geschichten Lesebuch (selections from: Poems Written Before Jumping Out of an 8 Story Window, The Days Run Away Like Wild Horses Over the Hills, Mockingbird Wish Me Luck), translated by Carl Weissner, Herbert Graf, Jürgen Theobaldy and Rolf Eckart John, Koln, Palmenpresse. 1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Flinke Killer (selections from: A Bukowski Sampler, Burning in Water Drowning in Flame, Crucifix in a Deathhand, Mockingbird Wish Me Luck, The Days Run Away Like Wild Horses Over the Hills, While the Music Played), translated by Carl Weissner and Rolf Eckart John, Köln, Palmenpresse. 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Western Avenue: Gedichte Aus Über 20 Jahren, 1955-1977 (selections from: It Catches My Heart in It Hands, Crucifix in a Deathhand, At Terror Street and Agony Way, The Days Run Away Like Wild Horses Over the Hills, Mockingbird Wish me Luck, Africa, Paris, Greece, Burning in Water Drowning in Flame, Maybe Tomorrow), translated by Carl Weissner, Frankfurt am Main, Zweitausendeins. 1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Terpentin on the Rocks: Die Bestes Gedichte Aus Der Amerikanischen Alternativpresse, 1966-1977, edited by C.B. and Carl Weissner, translated by Carl Weissner, Augsburg, Maro Verlag. C.B. poems on p. 15. 1978 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Kaputt In Hollywood (a selection from Erections, Ejaculations, Exhibitions and General Tales of Ordinary Madness), tranlsated by Carl Weissner, Augsburg, Maro Verlag. 1978 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Geburt, Leben Und Tod Einer Untergrundzeitung (a selection from Kaputt In Hollywood), translated by Carl Weissner, Heerhugowaard, Netherlands, Giftwerg-Presse. 1978 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Fuck Machine (a selection from Ejaculations...), translated by Wulf Teichmann, München, Carl Hanser Verlag. 1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Das Leben Und Sterben Im Uncle Sam Hotel ( a selection from Ejaculations...), translated by Carl Weissner, Augsburg, Maro Verlag. 1978 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Aufzeichnungen Eines Aussenseiters ( Notes Of A Dirty Old Man), translated by Carl Weissner, Frankfurt am Main, Fischer Taschenbuch Verlag. 1973 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Die Stripperinnen Vom Burbank ( South of No North), translated by Carl Weissner, Frankfurt am Main, Zweitausendeins. 1979 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Stories Und Romane ( South of No North, translated by Carl Weissner; Faktotum, translated by Carl Weissner; Der Mann Mit Der Ledertasche, translated by Hans Hermann; Anmerkugen Eines Dirty Old Man, translated by Carl Weissner, Frankfurt am Main, Zweitausendeins. 1977 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - L'Amour Est Un Chien De L'Enfer ( Love Is A Dog From Hell), translated by Gérard Guégan, Paris, Le Sagittaire - v.1 orange cover with C.B. drawing and v.2 pink cover with photo of C.B. 1978 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Factotum, translated by Marisa Caramella, Milano, Sugarco Edizioni. 1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Poesie (1955-1973), (selection from: It Catches My Heart In Its Hands, Crucifix In A Deathhand, At Terror Street and Agony Way, The Days Run Away Like Wild Horses Over the Hills, Mockingbird Wish me Luck, Burning In Water Drowning In Flame), uknown translator, Milano, Arnoldo Mondadori Editore. 1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - L'Amore É Un Cane Che Viene Dall'Inferno ( Love Is A Dog From Hell), translated by Paola Ludovici andGiogio Mariani, Roma, Savelli. 1979 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - A Sud Di Nessun Nord ( South of No North), translated by Marisa Caramella, Milano, Sugarco Edizioni. 1979 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Se Busca Una Mujer (South of No North), translated by Jorge García Berlanga, Barcelona, Editorial Anagrama. 1979 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Postkantoor ( Post Office), translated by Susan Janssen, Amsterdam, De Bezige Bij. 1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Offprint of a poem - source and translator unknown. No Date (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Offprint of a poem - source and translator unknown. No Date (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Post Office, London, London Magazine Editions. 1974 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Series VI: Miscellaneous Oversize Materials, Notes of a Dirty Old Man, 1976-1976
  Includes: Original appearances, reviews of C.B. books, interviews, commentary, book covers, book announcements, other miscellaneous writings, graffiti.
  - Open City (San Francisco). May 12, 1967-December 14, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Open City (San Francisco). December 29, 1967-December 26, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Open City (San Francisco). Also as an enclosure in San Francisco Phoenix #43, #47, and #54. January 24, 1967-March 6, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Times (Berkley). September 19, 1969-September 25, 1969. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Nola Express (New Orleans), #89-#107. 1971-June 8, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Nola Express (New Orleans), #109-#121. June 23, 1972-January 4, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Nola Express (New Orleans), #122-#134. January 4, 1973-July 5, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Nola Express (New Orleans), #135-#144. Also three early issues un-numbered and undated. July 13, 1974-December 13, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). March 17, 1967; February 11, 1972-July 14, 1972. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). July 21, 1972-December 22, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). January 5, 1973-April 27, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). May 11, 1973-October 26, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). November 2, 1973-December 28, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). January 4, 1974-March 22, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). March 29, 1974-May 31, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). June 14, 1974-October 4, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). October 11, 1974-December 20, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). January 3, 1975-May 29, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). May 30, 1975-August 28, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). August 29, 1975-January 1, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Free Press (Los Angeles). January 2, 1976-September 9, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Other Writings: Poetry, Prose Excerpts, Reviews. No Date (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Reviews of C.B. Books. No Date (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Interviews with and Commentary on C.B. No Date (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Other Magazine Appearances: Boulevards (interview), The Earth Rose (poems), Renaissance (poems/drawings), Renaissance (issue edited by C.B.). No Date (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Book Announcements and Covers: Flyers with Quotes and Drawings by C.B. No Date (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Graffiti. No Date (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Menu (for Linda Lee Beighle's restaurant) Drawn and Hand-lettered by C.B. No Date (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Readings: Announcements, Posters, Broadsides. No Date (Box 24)